BS SHRAVAN

Interaction Designer

heyshrav.com heyshrav@gmail.com

+91 9740269570

INTRODUCTION

I am currently a final year undergrad student at the Global Academy of Technology, Bengaluru.

As an Engineering student and a self-taught Designer, I try to bring my technical knowledge and design skills together to try and create meaningful designs and user experience.

Apart from having the experience of interning at 4 different startups and working on various freelance projects, I am also very passionate about photography and visual arts.

EXPERIENCE

LocTruth

UI/UX Intern

Worked on redesigning the main platform, marketing materials and assisted in front-end design implementation.

Mar 2021 - June 2021

Protoezy

Design Intern

Worked on brand identity design, wireframing & user interface design for a new sub-brand of Protoezy - Sourcetronics.

Dec 2021 - Jan 2021

KlapKlap

UI/UX Intern

Worked on conceptualizing user interface for iOS, improving in-app user experience and gamification process.

June 2020 - July 2020

Crimson Tech

Graphics Design Intern

Worked on creating marketing material, improving website UI, social media marketing designs and handling social media accounts.

May 2020 - Sept 2020

EDUCATION

Global Academy of Technology

Bachelor's of Engineering, Computer Science

2017 - 2021 I Bengaluru, India

Maharishi Vidya Mandir Sr. Secondary School

CBSE, PCM + Information Practices

2015 - 2017 | Noida, India

SKILLS

Design Skills

Soft Skills

Wireframing Team Leadership
Rapid Prototyping Project Management
Problem Solving Team Management
Design Thinking & Research Public Speaking

Design Tools

Technical Skills

Figma HTML
Adobe XD CSS
Adobe Illustrator Bootstrap
Adobe Photoshop ReactJS
Wireframe Sketching MySQL
Framer WordPress

OTHER WORK

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador Program

Alpha Student Ambassador

Learn Student Ambassadors are a global group of campus leaders who are eager to help fellow students, create robust tech communities and develop technical and career skills for the future.

Aug 2020 - Present

Upwork

Freelance Designer

Working as a Freelance Graphics & Web Designer on various projects in my free time for clients on Upwork.

Nov 2020 - Present